as Comics this is what we do it's our
job it's how we pay the bills okay so
all we ask is that from now on I know we
taping tonight but from now on you go to
a comedy show just enjoy just enjoy what
we've been told we're supposed to do
make people laugh at life cuz y'all are
life and y'all are
funny I'm serious I'm say there so many
people they got their phones and
they it's like what are you doing like
you came to a comedy show like you came
out to be entertained and you worrying
about somebody saying something that
offended you and it had nothing to do
with you so what I can say is this
before we get into the show um you know
if I say anything on this stage okay um
that you feel doesn't sit well with you
okay and you want to get up first of all
go that way don't come this
way that's
first uh secondly um I guess say I hope
God blesses you to get through whatever
it is that you felt was bothering you
that caused you to have to get up and
leave
okay I just bless somebody and people
are laughing at blessing y'all a little
lit here
bro but I also hope God blesses you uh
with Co and you die tonight
okay I just want to let you know where
I'm coming from y'all are killing me
with all this sensitivity and we can't
even just laugh at our own life this is
what we deal with like you know how
difficult it is for Comics like you know
like like I don't even mess with people
in the audience right like I don't mess
like I've never been good at cracking
jokes back at people right mainly for
two reasons while I'm on stage number
one I didn't see any Security checks
nobody uh checked
anybody so I know my position
okay that's number one uh two like like
come on man like I'm scared I just be
completely honest like I am scared I
don't know what people are going through
it's hard to know what people are going
through and then you take it on yourself
oo I'm going just say something back to
these people you don't know and people
are people are mentally ill these days
dog
so again you laughed at that I thought I
was being serious this this is going to
be a roller coaster set
here I mean I'm saying like when I was
in like grade school right I knew it was
never going to be good at snapping back
at people uh like I'd be sitting at the
cafeteria table right the lunch table
and some kid this is Elementary School
uh ooh Quincy like somebody just want to
be seen by everybody o Quincy your
mama's so fat she can hula hoop with the
rings of Saturn and everybody's like oh
his mama is
fat she is big and and I'm like oh man
and everybody's like you going to get
them Q you goingon to get them I'm like
yeah yeah yeah yeah and like I said I
don't know the line I don't know the
line so I come back I like well that's
that's why your mama died of AIDS and
she did
uh and everybody just like that oh come
on qu you don't come on man it's a joke
man you don't have to go down I'm like I
don't know the
[Laughter]
line so a lot of times I just stay away
from people man I don't I don't try to
deal with none of I I remember early in
my career I dealt with a Heckler right
so y'all know what a Heckler is at a
comedy show somebody to be heard over
the person who's got the mic right I'm
doing a show people are laughing as they
should have been enjoying the show and
over all the laughter I heard the
weirdest attention grabbing laugh
somebody wanted to be heard more than
everybody else so I'm saying my jokes
cry laugh over all the laughter I
hear immediately it caught my attention
I'm like who is this but the lights were
too bright I couldn't see in the crowd
you know and I get to the next joke sure
enough over all the crowd after uhuh I'm
like all right who
is who is trying to be a part of this
show and so then I kind of pinpoint
where where the i i is coming from right
so that's where I focus my next joke
sure enough right on time next joke I'm
like all right all right all right out
to you too right everybody's turning
around all right all right you keep that
up I'mma see you outside I didn't want
to see him outside but I thought I could
be tough by saying I'mma see him outside
right it got
worse he falling out the chair holding
on to his chair holding on to his inside
the crowd they forgot about me on stage
they turn around laughing with him I'm
getting upset hey man security cuz
somebody do something about the he
falling and everything and and I'm like
you know what I hope you die on your way
home tonight head on collision I hope
you die and everybody and people are
looking at me and I'm looking at them
and that's when we all realized he he
was choking on steak
my point is simple people I don't know
what's going on in your
[Applause]
life you don't know what's going on in
my life
just just let me have fun just let me do
this thing so I can go back home and
just safely safely
safely no matter what we all don't get
it right because we're human beings
right you know what I'm saying that's
why I have this message I wear it on my
wristband I wear it on my shirt as I
strive to be perfect but end up being
human right it's the best message out
here because people are so quick to
judge you so quick to point fingers and
and and and you know hold grudges and
and and and just and just look at you as
look like you're not perfect either
right we spent spend so much time doing
that and if we can stop doing this and
do more of this and lift people up I
think we could be a much better group of
people right because we can help each
other right
right prime example if you got an
opportunity to fix a flaw that you got
fellas some next summer time summer time
is over with next summer time use the
offseason to prepare your feet
[Laughter]
bro you didn't know I was going there
with it did you I'm serious man look I
got I got the problems too man I'm
missing a toenail on one foot I got dry
feet on the other one like like I'm I'm
very mix-matched okay on
my so I try to take the time to fix it
like you
know your foot is dry fellas
if when the back of your heel
uh resembles a Hardy's biscuit you know
how you can
just like you can we don't see you we
can hear you
coming it's a dry
foot ladies can't leave y'all out make
sure you fix your feet
too
okay sometimes uh you need to understand
next summer when the summer time comes
again if all your toes don't
fit in the open toe
shoe let that filter through the crowd
the shoe is open and all your toes don't
fit
you need to put on timbering boots with
your
bikini close all that stuff in I'm
serious y'all think I'm playing man look
I was uh cuz I live near the Virginia
Beach area right so every time at the
ocean front you know I'm saying I want
to make sure I can show this example and
y'all can understand what I saw I saw
these two women uh they were walking on
the beach perfect human just striving to
be perfect end up being human just they
didn't think nothing about their feet
didn't care y'all know the long toe that
y'all ladies have that long
toe that that toe hung off the front of
the sandal
just it twitched just like this it
moved as if it was helping her guide
herself around the
corner just just right there
just right up the front of the sandal
like as if it was a talent snatching
food for young
her friend right next to her she had a
pinky to her I can't make this up her
pinky told people it hung off the side
of the sandal as if it was the arm out
of a car window it was at
a it was at a perfect 45° angle right
there
just if you pushed her this way she was
done you pushed her over here she be
like kickstand toe you better leave me
[Applause]
alone try to be perfect end up being
human
man we all make mistakes man it's all
good it's all good look I can tell you
right now a little bit about myself uh
you know I'm a barber I'm a license
Professional Barber comedian also actor
and I also have a stutter I stutter Okay
the reason why I don't do it on stage is
because I don't do it in front of people
I don't
know y'all are getting a representative
I don't know any of
you okay once we become cool I'll
probably mess up two hours of the rest
of your night I'm
sorry I never forget like I ran into to
a partner of mine like we haven't seen
each other in a long time he stutters as
well right I ran it to him and uh when
two people who stutter see each other no
matter how bad our stutter is we have to
talk that was the longest hello that
almost never manifested
itself cuz I saw him and I'm like
[Laughter]
hey he looking at me just
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
what's up man three days for that
transaction